Ubu Repertory Theater Script Collection ca. 1982-1994 MSS 120 MSS.120
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: English Manuscripts
  - Bourgeade, Pierre. 'Deutsches Requiem', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 58)
  - Bourget, Elizabeth. 'Bonne F Maman', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 59)
  - Bouteille, Romain. 'The Twilight of the Diplomats', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 60)
  - Boyer, Frans. 'Does God Bark? adapted by Marc Serhan', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 61)
  - Brassard, Jean. 'Where the Water Runs Deep', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 62)
  - Brewster, Thomas. 'The Bougival Vampire', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 63)
  - Brincourt, Frans. 'Royal Flush', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 64)
  - Bronsard, Marie. 'The Hermitage', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 65)
  - Burgaud, Jean Pierre and Versari, Jean Charles. 'Fragments #1', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 66)
  - Butake, Bole and Doho, Gilbert. 'Zintgraff and the Battle of Mankon', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 67)
  - Caban, G. 'The Pharaoh Cannot Die', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 68)
  - Camus, Albert. 'The Just', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 69)
  - Camus, Albert. 'The Misunderstanding', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 70)
  - Canac-Marquis, Normand. 'Children of Urantia', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 71)
  - Carone, Catherine. 'The Spendthrift', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 72)
  - Cire, Ina. 'Island Memories: Mama N. and Mama F.', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 73)
  - Cire, Aim'Notebook of a Return to the Native Land', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 74)
  - Cendrars, Blaise. 'Sarajevo. adapted by Jean-Max Guieu', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 75)
  - Chalem, Denise. Crystal Night', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 76)
  - Champagne, Dominic. 'Playing Bare', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 77)
  - Champagne, Dominic. 'The Rehearsal', undated; 31142040610449 (Box II.2, Folder 78)
  - Charlier, Jacques Rey. 'From Noon to Lent: A Mortal Audience', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 79)
  - Charlier, Jacques Rey. 'From Noon to Lent: Requiem Mardi-Gras', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 80)
  - Charlier, Jacques Rey. 'Lizard/Lazarus', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 81)
  - Charyn, Jerome. 'George', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 82)
  - Chaurette, Normand. 'Fragments of a Farewell Letter Read by Geologists', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 83)
  - Chaurette, Normand. 'Provincetown Playhouse July 1919', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 84)
  - Chawaf, Chantal. 'Warmth: A Bloodsong', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 85)
  - Chd, Andr 'The Goddess Lar', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 86)
  - Chd, Andr 'Queen in Check', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 87)
  - Chenus, Sylvie. 'The Lost Paradise Club. adapted by Thomas Weber', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 88)
  - Chesnot, Pierre. Rude Awakening. adapted by Mawby Green and Ed Feilbert', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 89)
  - Chevallier, Louis. Agatha', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 90)
  - Cixous, Hne. 'The Name of Oedipus: Song of the Forbidden Body', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 91)
  - Cixous, Hne. 'Portrait of Dora', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 92)
  - Claudel, Paul. 'The Trade', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 93)
  - Cocteau, Jean. 'Le Bel Indifferent', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 94)
  - Cocteau, Jean. 'The Knights of the Round Table', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 95)
  - Cohen, Arnold Lewis. 'Oasis in the Dark', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 96)
  - Collette, Jean and Cecchinato, Toni. 'Hangar of the Bygones', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 97)
  - CondMaryse. 'Death of Oluwemi of Ajumako', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 98)
  - CondMaryse. 'The Hills of Massabielle', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 99)
  - Confort Claude. 'The Marathon', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 100)
  - Corbier, Annie. 'L.', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 101)
  - Cormann, Enzo. 'The Drifter', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 102)
  - Cormann, Enzo. 'Exiles', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 103)
  - Cormann, Enzo. 'Noises', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 104)
  - da Costa, Bernard. 'Boomerang!', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 105)
  - da Costa, Bernard. 'The Farewells of the Grand Duchess', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 106)
  - da Costa, Bernard. 'The Meeting of Cleopatra and the Queen of Saba', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 107)
  - da Costa, Bernard. 'We Charles XII', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 108)
  - Cousse, Raymond. 'Kid's Stuff', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 109)
  - Cousse, Raymond. 'Strategy for Two Hams', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 110)
  - Cousse, Raymond. 'Swine's Way or Strategy for Two Hams', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 111)
  - Curtay, Jean-Paul. 'Letterism and Hypergraphics: The Unknown Avant-Garde', undated; 31142040610456 (Box II.3, Folder 112)
  - Dambury, Gerty. 'Crosscurrents', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 113)
  - Danaud, Jean-Claude. 'Casanova's Babies', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 114)
  - Danis, Daniel. 'Stone and Ashes', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 115)
  - Delaunay, Constance. 'The Curtains', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 116)
  - Delbo, Charlotte. 'Who Will Carry the Word?', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 117)
  - Demarcy, Richard. 'The Stranger in the House', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 118)
  - Deslias, Philippe. 'Geronimo', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 119)
  - Deutsch, Michel. 'Body and Blood', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 120)
  - Deutsch, Michel. 'Thermidor (first draft)', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 121)
  - Deutsch, Michel. 'Thermidor', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 122)
  - Deutsch, Michel. 'Sunday', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 123)
  - Didier-Weill, Alain. 'The Bench', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 124)
  - Diderot, Denis. 'The Illegitimate Son (incomplete)', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 125)
  - Diop, Birago. 'Mor Lam's Bone', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 126)
  - Doriadis, Andonis. 'It's Hell, My Love', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 127)
  - Doriadis, Andonis. 'Oh, Actors', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 128)
  - Doriadis, Andonis. 'Who's Who?', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 129)
  - Doutreligne, Louise. 'When Speedoux Goes to Sleep', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 130)
  - Dubillard, Roland. 'The Swallows', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 131)
  - Dubois, Renaniel. 'Being at Home with Claude', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 132)
  - Dubois, Renaniel. 'But Laura Didn't Answer', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 133)
  - Dufresne, Isabelle C. 'High Hopes', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 134)
  - Dufresne, Isabelle. 'The Trial', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 135)
  - Dumont, Maxime. 'Boat People', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 136)
  - Dupoyet, Pierrette. 'Madame Guillotin', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 137)
  - Duras, Marguerite. 'Agatha', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 138)
  - Duras, Marguerite. 'Agatha (different translation)', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 139)
  - Duras, Marguerite. 'The Eden Cinema', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 140)
  - Duras, Marguerite. 'The Square', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 141)
  - Duras, Marguerite. 'Vera Baxter', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 142)
  - Duras, Marguerite. 'The Viaducts of Seine-et-Oise', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 143)
  - Durringer, Xavier. 'Murder in Mind', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 144)
  - Dussault, Louisette. 'Mommy', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 145)
  - Ebner, Jacques. 'Just a Touch', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 146)
  - Ernotte, Andr'The Camel Has His Nose Under the Tent', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 147)
  - Ernotte, Andr'Jacques Brel Blues', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 148)
  - Etcherelli, Claire. 'Germinal, Year III', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 149)
  - Fabre d'Eglantine, Pierre-Frans-Nicolas. 'Intrigue by Letter', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 150)
  - Faure, Philippe. 'Still Life for 3 Dancers', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 151)
  - Fenwick, Jean-No 'Race to Glory', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 152)
  - Fenwick, Jean-No Joffo, Francis; Lambert, Lucien.[letter from Norman Stokle to Ubu Repretory asking to publish three playwrites], undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 152a.)
  - Feydeau, Georges. 'Much I do About Nothing. adapted by Rollin DeVere', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 153)
  - Filho, Oduvaldo Vianna. Papa Highirte', undated; 31142040610464 (Box II.4, Folder 154)
  - Filloux, Catherine. 'The Price of Madness', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 155)
  - Fornes, Maria Irene. 'The Mothers', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 156)
  - Foucher, Mich. 'The Table: Womenspeak', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 157)
  - Fourcade, Gauthier. 'A Certain Oedipus', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 158)
  - Fritsch, Luc. 'Ruins', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 159)
  - Gallaire, Fatima. 'House of Wives', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 160)
  - Garneau, Michel. 'Four to Four', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 161)
  - Garneau, Michel. 'Strauss and Pesant (and Rosa)', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 162)
  - Gatti, Armand. 'The 7 Possibilities for Train713 Departing from Auschwitz', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 163)
  - Gazarian, Pierre. 'Professor Sombrero and His Students', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 164)
  - Gazarian, Pierre. 'Customs', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 165)
  - Gazarian, Pierre. 'Sitting Down - Liberty, Pizza Pie, Lily and Ruby', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 166)
  - Genet, Jean. 'Hymn and Her', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 167)
  - Genet, Jean. 'Splendid's', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 168)
  - Genvrin, Emmanuel. (adaptor). 'Black Slavery', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 169)
  - Genvrin, Emmanuel. The Etuves followed by Black Slavery, undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 170)
  - Gershman, Judith. 'Dark Sun', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 171)
  - Gingras, Ren'Breaks', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 172)
  - Giraudoux, Jean. 'The Apollo of Bellac', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 173)
  - Grumberg, Jean-Claude. 'L'Atelier', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 174)
  - Grumberg, Jean-Claude. 'The Brawl', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 175)
  - Grumberg, Jean-Claude. 'The Indian Under Babylon', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 176)
  - Grumberg, Jean-Claude. 'Mama'll Be Back Poor Orphan', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 177)
  - Grumberg, Jean-Claude. 'On Vacation', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 178)
  - Guimet, Jacques. 'The Painter's Studio (final version)', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 179)
  - Guimet, Jacques. 'The Painter's Studio', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 180)
  - Hafkin, Joel and Snow, William. 'Ordinary Magic', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 181)
  - Ha Victor. 'Abraham and Samuel', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 182)
  - Ha Victor. The Abyss or The Chasm or The Crevasse or The Ravine (Take Your Pick!)', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 183)
  - Ha Victor. 'The Dance of Chance. adapted by Jack Trahey', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 184)
  - Ha Victor. Family Flesh', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 185)
  - Ha Victor. 'The Fruit of a Burned Out Tree', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 186)
  - Ha Victor. 'The Guest of Honor', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 187)
  - Ha Victor. 'How to Harpoon the Shark', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 188)
  - Ha Victor. 'Isaac and the Midwife', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 189)
  - Ha Victor. 'No Appointment', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 190)
  - Ha Victor. 'Tune Your Violins', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 191)
  - Ha Victor. 'The Vampire Always Bites Twice', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 192)
  - Hakim, Adel. 'Executioner 14', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 193)
  - Harris, Willie Thomas. 'The Beginning of the Marathon', undated; 31142040610472 (Box II.5, Folder 194)
  - Ionesco, Eugene. 'The Bald Soprano', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 195)
  - Ionesco, Eugene. 'The Chairs', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 196)
  - Ionesco, Eugene. 'The Future Is in Eggs', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 197)
  - Ionesco, Eugene. 'Jacques or Obedience', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 198)
  - Ionesco, Eugene. 'Jack or The Submission', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 199)
  - Ionesco, Eugene. 'Journeys Among the Dead', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 200)
  - Ionesco, Eugene. 'The Taming of Jack', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 201)
  - IsraLe Pelletier, Marc and Frankston, Peggy. 'The Globe', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 201a.)
  - Jarry, Alfred. 'Ubu Cocu', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 202)
  - Jelinek, Elfriede. 'Illness or Modern Women', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 203)
  - Joffo, Francis. 'Oh, Grandad! (synopsis only)', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 204)
  - Jouhandeau, Marcel. 'Elise', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 205)
  - Jouvet, Louis. 'Elvire Jouvet 40', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 206)
  - Jouvet, Louis. 'Seven Lessons (from Elvire Jouvet 40)', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 207)
  - Kacimi, Mohamed. '1962', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 208)
  - Kalinoski, Richard. 'A Beast on the Moon', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 209)
  - Kalisky, Ren'Aida Defeated', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 210)
  - Kaye, Richard. 'The Neglected Hypotenuse', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 211)
  - Keineg, Paol. 'The Springtime of the Red Caps', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 212)
  - Kesselman, Wendy. 'The Butcher's Daughter', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 213)
  - Kesselman, Wendy. 'My Sister in this House', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 214)
  - Klr, Frans. 'Jacques "The Fatalist"', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 215)
  - Kobrynski, Lazare. 'The Lady with the Little Dog', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 216)
  - Kolt Bernard-Marie. 'In the Loneliness of the Cottonfields', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 217)
  - Kolt Bernard-Marie. 'Key West', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 218)
  - Kolt Bernard-Marie. 'Quay West', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 219)
  - Kolt Bernard-Marie. 'Roberto Zucco', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 220)
  - Kolt Bernard-Marie. 'Roberto Zucco', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 221)
  - Kribus, Serge. 'Boris Spielman's Big Comeback (first version)', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 222)
  - Kribus, Serge. 'Boris Spielman's Big Comeback', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 223)
  - Kundera, Milan. 'Jacques and his Master', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 224)
  - KwahulKoffi. 'Bintu', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 225)
  - Laberge, Marie. 'Aure, Ma Soeur', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 226)
  - Laberge, Marie. 'Deep Night', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 227)
  - Labiche, Eug and Michel, Marc. 'La Dame aux Jambes d'Azur (original)', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 228)
  - Labiche, Eug and Michel, Marc. 'La Dame aux Jambes d'Azur', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 229)
  - Labiche, Eug and Martin, Edouard. 'The Voyage of Monsieur', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 230)
  - Laleau, L and Lr, Georges N. 'On the Case', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 231)
  - Lambert, Lucien. 'Sunrise at Noon', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 232)
  - Laou, Julius-Am. 'Daughter of Ham the Accursed', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 233)
  - Laville, Pierre. 'The Blue Spring', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 234)
  - Laville, Pierre. 'The Red River', undated; 31142040610480 (Box II.6, Folder 235)
  - Legault, Anne. 'O'Neill', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 236)
  - Legault, Anne. 'A Winter's Tale', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 237)
  - Lepage, Robert. 'Da Vinci', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 238)
  - Lepoutre, Raymond. 'Dreaming Up America', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 239)
  - Lescure, Pierre. 'Jacob or The Fight Against God', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 240)
  - Lescure, Pierre. 'Luridan', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 241)
  - Lsque, L 'When I Told Her ThatShe Started to Laugh', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 242)
  - Lewis, Reginald Sinclair. 'An Affinity for Angels', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 243)
  - Liegme, Bernard. 'Tandem', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 244)
  - Liking, Werewere. 'Paper Heroes', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 245)
  - Liking, Werewere. 'Singue Mura: Given that a Woman', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 246)
  - Louvet, Jean. 'Simenon', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 247)
  - Makhele, Caya. 'The Fable of the Cloister of Cemeteries', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 248)
  - Mallat, Robert. 'Nuremberg 96', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 249)
  - Malraux, Alain. 'So Far, So Good', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 250)
  - Malraux, Alain. 'Whitsun', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 251)
  - Manet, Edouardo. 'The Day Mary Shelly Met Charlotte Bronte', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 252)
  - Manet, Edouardo. The Day Mary Shelly Met Charlotte Bronte.' (new revised version), undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 253)
  - Manet, Edouardo. 'Mendoza, In Argentina', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 254)
  - Mann, Klaus. 'Mephisto', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 255)
  - Marcellin, Marianne. 'Curtains!', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 256)
  - Marcellin, Marianne. 'Staircase B, Third Floor', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 257)
  - Marchessault, Jovette. 'The End of the Earth Is Too Near, Violette Leduc', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 258)
  - Martin, Alexis. 'Matroni and I', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 259)
  - McGibbon, Jim and Marcelle. The Siege of St. Antoine's or The Whores of St.Antoine's', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 260)
  - Mercure, Marthe. 'Blood Sisters', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 261)
  - Michoux, Henri. 'The Constructor's Drama', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 262)
  - Micone, Marco. 'Addolorata', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 263)
  - Minyana, Philippe. 'Boomerang or The Red Living Room', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 264)
  - Minyana, Philippe. 'Chambres', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 265)
  - Minyana, Philippe. 'Summer's End at Baccarat', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 266)
  - Moli. 'Don Juan', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 267)
  - Moli. The Misanthrope;' adapted by Alan DiBona and Lauren Marshall, undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 267a.)
  - Moli. 'Tartuffe', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 268)
  - Montherlant, Henri de. 'Don Juan or a Death on the Sidewalk', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 269)
  - Montherlant, Henri de. 'The Exile', undated; 31142040610498 (Box II.7, Folder 270)
  - Moreau, Isabelle. 'The Studious Actor or Kattie's Dream', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 271)
  - Muehlberger, Erik. 'Ms. Smith', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 272)
  - Mujomba, Pierre Mumbere. 'The Lost Envelope (final version)', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 273)
  - Mujomba, Pierre Mumbere. 'The Lost Envelope', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 274)
  - Namiand, Arlette. 'Especially When Night Falls', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 275)
  - Navarre, Yves. 'It's RainingWhy Don't We Kill Mum and Dad?', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 276)
  - Navarre, Yves. 'The Suitcases', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 277)
  - Ndao, Cheik. 'La Dsion', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 278)
  - Nocher, Frans. 'Chekhov Chekhova', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 279)
  - Novak, Beata. 'Don't Disturb the President', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 280)
  - Novarina, Val. 'Letter to the Actors', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 281)
  - N'tumb, Diur. 'Zaina', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 282)
  - Nyiri, Janos. 'The Dream-Ladder', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 283)
  - Obey, Andr'Noah', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 284)
  - Olmi, Vnique. 'A Touch of the Scorpion', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 285)
  - Pagnol, Marcel. 'Marius', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 286)
  - Palustran, Christian. 'A Yellow Butterfly Called Sphinx', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 287)
  - Palustran, Christian. 'A Yellow Butterfly Called Sphinx', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 288)
  - Pedneault, Hne. 'Evidence to the Contrary', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 289)
  - Pelletier, Maryse. 'Pas de Deux for Obstinate Voices', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 290)
  - Pelletier, Pol. 'White Light', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 291)
  - Philip, Michel. 'Father and Son', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 292)
  - Philip, Michel. 'George and Frric or Dead Embers', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 293)
  - Philip, Michel. 'Mourning', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 294)
  - Philip, Michel. 'Sons of the Sun', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 295)
  - Picasso, Pablo. 'Catch Desire by the Tail', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 296)
  - Picasso, Pablo. 'Catch Desire by the Tail', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 297)
  - Pozzuoli, Alain. 'The Last Blues', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 298)
  - Prnt, Henri. 'The Train of the Time', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 299)
  - Prnt, Henri. 'The Rhyming Prophetess', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 300)
  - Pressmann, Elie. 'Day and Night', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 301)
  - Pressmann, Elie. 'Day and Night', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 302)
  - Pressmann, Elie. 'Fiddler Off the Wall', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 303)
  - Pressmann, Elie. 'Odd Man Out', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 304)
  - Pressmann, Elie. 'The Sound of Wings', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 305)
  - Prevand, Jean-Frans. 'Sartre It's Me Camus!', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 306)
  - Py, Olivier. 'The Exaltation of the Labyrinth', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 307)
  - Rafenomanjato, Charlotte. 'The Herd', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 308)
  - Raffalli, Bernard. 'Marie-Antoinette', undated; 31142040610506 (Box II.8, Folder 309)